https://www.fairwayneedlecraft.com/zencart/privacy.html

Brands
FAIRWAY NEEDLEC..
About Us
Welcome to our Store!
Fairway Needlecraft was started by two brothers and their father in 1919.
One brother would print the embroidery pattern on doilies while the other brother would take his bicycle and go to local stores and sell these doilies by the gross.
Their father financed this project.
As the business grew they moved from the upstairs of the fathers house to their first factory location.The depression came and they survived by making ladies aprons.
The business still continued to grow and finally the two brothers split the business, one continuing on with stamped embroidery and the other selling novelty items under the name of Fairway Manufacturing.Fairway Needlecraft moved from the city of St. Louis to its current location in St. Clair
where the factory is located today.
Three generation later, Fairway Needlecraft is still producing high quality stamped for embroidery items.We currently have a very complete line of embroidery items to purchase.
A large selection of quilt blocks, with or without quilting marks. There are many different designs, some with only cross stitch, others with different embroidery stitches or a combination of both cross stitch and embroidery.Doilies with perle edge or with lace will accent any roomDresser scarves with either perle edge or lace edge are available to match our pillowcases and doilies.Pillowcases with perle, lace or our very own ruffled edge to enhance any bedroom.
There are many different designs and many different themes.An area that we are continuing to develop is our Kids crafts.
Currently we have our "Just Color It" pillowcases that are great for birthday parties or 4H project.
The "Learn to Stitch" teaches children how to stitch and make an accent pillow for their bedroom.
The newest addition to this area is our "Wall Art".
This is a unique craft that encompasses painting, stitching, and fabric dyeing.Infant items are always good gifts.
Our 9x9 inch baby blocks or 36x50 inch baby tops offer many different designs to choose from.
Info
General Info
About Us
Site Map
Gift Certificate FAQ
Discount Coupons
Newsletter Unsubscribe
Customers
$14.50
For customers in the US all orders will be sent using the United States Postal Service with the following rates to apply.
Order Value
Postage Added
0 - $30
$10.50
$30.01 - $60.00
$18.00
$60.01 - $100.00
$25.00
And up
$40.00
For customers in Canada all orders will be sent through the Canadian Postal Service with the following rates to apply:
Shop with Confidence
You will be able to purchase all items on the website knowing that a full refund is available for any defects.
When checking out you can use any credit card. Use the paypal button and follow all links. It will allow you to use your own credit card without needing a paypal accout.
For those customers who choose not to use a credit card an order form can be printed off of the website. Follow the instruction provided on the order form.
Shopping Cart - 0 item(s) - $0.00
Log In
Shop
Embroidered Clock
KID CRAFTS
PILLOWCASES
STANDARD EMBROIDERY
CROSS STITCH
Categories
Embroidered ClockKID CRAFTSPILLOWCASES->QUILT BLOCKS->INFANT ITEMS->DRESSER SCARVES->CHRISTMAS->QUILT BORDERSGift CertificatesDOILIESTOWELSSpecials ...New Products ...All Products ...
What's New  [more]
BORDER PATTERN 492$30.00
BORDER PATTERN 292$30.00
BORDER PATTERN 295$30.00
Home ::
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Fairway Needlecraft's commitent to Privacy
Your privacy is important to us.  To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on Fairway Needlecraft's website.  On some pages, you can order products, make request and register to receive materials.  The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Credit/Debit card information
(etc)
On some pages, you can submit information about other people.  If you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address.  In this circumstane, the types of personal information collected are:
Name
Address
Phone number
(etc.)
We use the informatin you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order  We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery.  We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessar to complete that order.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.  Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online inways unrelated to  ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to optout or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and insure the correct us of information, we have put in place appropiate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by emailing us directly.  We use this procedure to better safeguard you information.
You can correct factual errors in your presonally identifiable information be sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify you identity before granting access or making corrections
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at info@fairwayneedlecraft.com
Reviews  [more]
I would LOVE to see this in a quilt block, would make a...
Quick LinksHomeFeatured ProductsSpecialsWhat's NewAll Products ...
InformationAbout UsSite MapGift Certificate FAQDiscount CouponsNewsletter Unsubscribe
Customer ServiceContact UsShipping & ReturnsPrivacy NoticeConditions of UseMy Account
Copyright © 2020 Fairway Needlecraft Co..
Developed by ZenCartPros.com.
